

Muhammad **Asad**

MERN Stack Developer

ABOUT ME

I am Full Stack MERN Developer. having experience in JavaScript, Node JS, React, Python, Restful API's, PHP, UX/UI, HTML, CSS, Boot Strap, Tailwind CSS, semantic UI, WordPress. I also have additional skills of Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, premiere pro and many more.

CONTACT ME



+92 3126399437



asad.tufail199913@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/asadtufail-b29386178/



https://asadzportfolio.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

(Comsats University Islamabad, Sahiwal Campus) 2018 - 2022

Final Year Project: Taskwud (Organization management Web Application using Machine Learning)

WORK EXPERIENCE

User Experience Hub (Pvt) Ltd

(Onsite)

Aug 2022 - Present

I have been working as a freelancer for almost three years now. I have done multiple projects of Web development and designing.

Response Alert

(Onsite)

June 2022 - Present

I have been working as a freelancer for almost three years now. I have done multiple projects of Web development and designing.

FREELANCER

(Fiver)

2019 - 2022

I have been working as a freelancer for almost three years now. I have done multiple projects of Web development and designing.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Kunshuish

(http://kunshuisoord.com/)

Kunshuis is a platform which help designer to earn a financial income. Where designers can design their shirts and sell them

Ramay Autos

(2021)

It is an E commerce store for selling and buying cars (just like Pak wheels with some extra features)

Taskwud

(2021-2022)

Organization management Web Application using Machine Learning (Resembles Asana, Jira but with many automated features like scheduling and auto assigning of tasks using Machine learning)

Response Alert

(2022)

Response Alert is a Medical Alert company devoted to the placement and care of personal emergency response systems (PERS) for your loved ones.

SKILLS ME

HTML/CSS3 ••••••	JavaScript	•••••
React JS ••••••	Node JS/Express	••••••
Video Editing	Graphic Designing	•••••
Photo Editing	PHP/Asp.net/Pythor	1 • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • •